Academic Affairs and Provost, Office of Senior V.P. for; Records ua500
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Administrative Records, 1950-2021; 8; 21.03 cubic ft.
  - SUNY Intensive Training Proposal to HEW, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Task Force on Adult Education, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Developmental Science Courses, 1972; Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Allen Collegiate Center - Budget, 1972; 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Search Committee for the Dean of the School of Education, 1972; 1973; 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Allen Collegiate Center, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Retrenchment, 1972; 1974; 1975; 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - School of Nursing Graduate Program Feasibility Study, 1972-1976; Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Calendars, 1972-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Convening Meetings on Religious Holidays, 1972; 1977; 1978; 1979; 1981 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Program Proposal and Review Guidelines, 1972-1973; 1977; 1979-1983; Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Facilities Usage Policy, 1973 May 30 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Chancellors Committee on Open Access, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1973; Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Part-Time Employment, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Recommended Procedures and Policies for Promotions and Continuing Appointments, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Ford Foundation, Venture Fund Program, 1973; 1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Third World Media Arts, 1973; 1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Public Policy Planning, 1973; 1974; 1975; Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Department of Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1973; 1977; 1978; 1979 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Workload, 1973; 1975-1984; Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs - Organization, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Priorities and Resource Allocation, Deans, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Change in Liberal Education, 1974; Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Poverty Research Center, 1974; 1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Milne School - Phase Out, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Twelve to Ten Month Conversion, 1974; 1975; 1976 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Division of Social and Behavioral Sciences - Annual Reports, 1974; 1975; 1976; 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Correspondce - Academic Deans and Department Chairs, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Resource Allocation Policy, 1974-1981; Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Graduate School of Public Affairs - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975 September (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - School of Criminal Justice - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975 September (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Division of Humanities - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Division of Science and Mathematics - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Division of Social and Behavioral Sciences - Administrative and Evaluation, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - School of Business - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - School of Social Welfare - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975 October (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - International Women's Year, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Priorities and Resource Allocation, Deans, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - School of Library and Information Science - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - School of Education - Administrative Self Study and Evaluation, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - University Affairs, Evaluations (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - University Affairs, Evaluations (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - University Affairs, Evaluations (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Department of Astronomy and Space Science, 1975; Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - College of General Studies - Administrative Self-Study and Evaluation, 1975; 1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - University Commission on Purpose and Priorities, 1975; 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Educational Communications Center, Program in Support of Instructional Desgin, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Allen Collegiate Center Evaluation, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Computing Center, Self-Study and Evaluation, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Educational Opportunities Program Evaluations, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Search Committee for Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Task force - Position Cuts, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - University-Regional Interaction, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - College of Arts and Sciences - Organization, 1976; Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Shorter Work Year, 1976; Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Search Committee for the Vice President of Academic Affairs, Final Report, ca. 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Retrenchment, 1976; 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Task force - Program Actions, 1976; 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - School of Nursing - Phase out, 1976; 1977; 1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Weighted Student Credit Hours Model, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Ad-Hoc Writing Committee, 1977; 1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Retrenchment, 1977; 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Program Phase out, 1977; 1978; Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Environmental Studies, 1977; 1978; 1979; Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - School of Education - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1977-1978; 1983-1984; 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - School of Education - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1977-1979; 1983-1984; 1986-1992 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1977-1978; 1981-1989; 1991-1994; Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Schweitzer and Einstein Chair, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Meeting of Two-Year Colleges Deans, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Improvement of Undergraduate Teaching, 1979; 1980 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Personnel Activity Reporting System - Procedures, 1980 July 28 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Chicago Circle Performance Ratio, 1980; Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy - Program Development, 1980-1984; Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence - Academic Deans and Department Chairs, 1980; 1981; 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Departmental Profiles, 1981; 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Professional Staff Development, 1981; 1982; 1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bureau of Veterans of Education, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1982; 1985; 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Assistants Stipends, 1982-1986; 1990; 1996; Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, 1983; 1984; 1985; Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Convocation, 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Minority Student Services, 1983; 1984; 1985; 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Program Proposal and Review - Guidelines and Procedures, 1983; 1986-1988; 1990; 1995; Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Program Deactivation, 1983; 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Office of Judicial Affairs, Academic Integrity Policies, 1983-1998; Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - School of Business, 1983; 1999-2002; Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - UAlbany-University of Belgrade Academic and Cultural Exchange Program, proposal, 1984 March (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - New York Institution for Telecommunications, 1984 April 16 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Center for Research and Development, a propectus, 1984 May (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Proposal to Establish a Mid-Hudson Institute of Management Training, Development, and Research, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - College of Science and Mathematics, 1984-1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Diversity Materials, 1984; 1985; 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Assessment, 1984; 1988; 1990-1994; Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Search file - Assistant to the Vice President for Research and Educational Development, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Assessment, 1985-1988; Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Sabbatical Leave, 1985; 1989-1991; 1995; 1999; 2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Orientation Handbook, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Department of Educational Administration and Policy Studies, 1986; 1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, 1986; 1987; Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Department of Program Development and Evaluation, 1985; 1987; 1988 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Racial Concerns Across the Campus, 1986-1989; Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Department of Teacher Education, 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Diversity Materials, 1986; 1988-1991; Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Assessment, 1986; 1988-1992; Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Assessment, 1986; 1988-1992; Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Department of Slavic Languages and Literatures, 1986; 1989; 1990; 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Center for Computing and Disablility, 1986-1994; Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments - Promoting Rosters, 1986-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Guide to Audio Visual Resources and Services, 1987 September (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Workload, 1987; 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - University Support Services, 1987; 1988; Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Academic Policy Group, 1987; 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Academic Policy Group, 1987; 1990; Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Distinguished Professorship Guidelines, 1987; 1988; 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Diversity, 1987; 1989-1991; 1993; 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - General Education Honors Program, 1987; 1988; 1990; 1992; 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Workload, 1987-1989; 1991-1994; Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Study Abroad Programs - Moscow, Madrid, ca. 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Guidelines for the Preparation of Recommendations for Promotions and Continuing Appointments, 1988 August (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "A Practical Guide to Chairing an Academic Department", 1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Racial Concerns Across the Campus, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Deans' Retreat, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Deans' Retreat, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Diversity - California State University Task Force Report, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "Teaching and Learning at the University at Albany: A Guide for Faculty", 1988 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Self-Study Report (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Self-Study Report (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1988; 1989 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Deans' Retreat, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Diversity Bibliography, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Diversity Course Examples - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Five Year Plan - 1988-89 to 1992-93, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Diversity articles and clips, 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Diversity Committees, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Department of Educational Theory and Practice, 1988; 1989; 1990; 1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - College of Arts and Sciences - Planning and Transition, 1988; 1990; 1991; 1992 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Rockefeller College Professional Development Program, 1988-2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Policy Guidelines (SUNY), 1988; 1990; 1994; 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Diversity - University Senate Bill, 1989 April 28 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Capital Campaign, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Capital Campaign Project Proposals, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Deans' Retreat, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Diversity Committee Chairs Meeting, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Diversity Meeting, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Academic Policy Group, 1989; 1990 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1989; 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Department of Educational Psychology and Studies, 1989; 1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Diversity Candidates, 1989; 1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Five Year Plan Progress Report, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Search file - Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1989; 1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Assessment, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Campus Forum - Eastern Europe Forum, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Campus Forum - Planning Group, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Campus Forum - Salisbury, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Capital Campaign, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - College of Arts and Sciences - Task force on University Organization, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Department of Educational Psychology and Statistics, 1989; 1990; 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Diversity Committee Chairs, 1989; 1990; 1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Distinguished Professorship - Policies and Procedures, 1989-1991; Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Workload, 1989; 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - School of Criminal Justice - Planning, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - College of Science and Mathematics, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Diversity Committee Chairs, 1989; 1990; 1992; 1993 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Utilization Policy, 1989-1991; 1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Utilization Audit, 1989; 1990; 1991; 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Deans Retreat, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Diversity Committee Chairs Meeting, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Doctoral Council (1 of 3), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Doctoral Council (2 of 3), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Doctoral Council (3 of 3), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Establishment of a Department of East Asian Studies, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Portuguese Language Program, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Search File - Dean of Social and Behavioral Studies, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Forum Planning Group, 1990; Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Department of Reading, 1990; 1991 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Diversity Committees - Reports, 1990; 1991 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Assessment, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Campus Forum, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Campus Forum, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Campus Forum - Charles, Gati, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Diversity Materials, 1990; 1991; Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Diversity Requirements, 1990; 1992 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - SUNY 2000, 1990; 1991; 1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Assessment (1 of 2), 1990; 1992; 1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Assessment (2 of 2), 1990; 1992; 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - College of Arts and Science - Commitments to Department Chairs, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Workload, 1990; 1991; 1992; 1994 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry Building, 1990; 1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Cypriot Studies, 1990; 1999; Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Programs, 1990; 1996; 1998-2000; 2002; 2004 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - School of Education, 1990; 2001-2003; 2005 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Divesity Committee Members, ca. 1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - College of Science and Mathematics, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, 1991; 1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Enivironmental Studies, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Doctoral Council - Program Review Procedures, 1991; 1992; 1997; Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Doctoral Council, 1991; 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Department of Economics, 1991-1997; 1999; 2002 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Central for Electronic Language Learning and Research (CELLAR), 1991; 1992; 2001; 2002; Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Liberty Partnership Program, 1991-1992; 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs (1 of 2), 1991; 1993-1998; 2001-2003; Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs (2 of 2), 1991; 1993-1998; 2001-2003; Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Outcomes Assessment at Albany - A Report to the State University of New York, 1992 June (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1992; Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Department of Arts, 1992; Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Diversity Committees Reports, 1992; 1993 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - School of Education, 1992; 1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - SED Doctoral Program Review, 1992; 1993; 1994 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - School of Education, 1992-1994; Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Department of Geological Sciences, Department of Earth and Atmospheric Sciences, 1992; 1993; 1994; 1995 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Assessment, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - SUNY 2000, 1992; 1995; Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Governmental Relations, 1992; 1993; 2001; 2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Assessment (1 of 2), 1992; 1995; 1997-2003; Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Assessment (2 of 2), 1992; 1995; 1997; 1999-2003; Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - College of Arts and Science - Planning and Inauguration, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Doctoral Project Task Force, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - First Cities, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, 1993; 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, 1993; 1994; 1995 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1993; 1994; 1995; 1996 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Department of Africana Studies, 1993; 1994; 1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - CETL, 1993-1995; 1998-2000; Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Department of Athletics, 1993-1996; 2001; Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Fuller Road Management Corporation, 1993; 2001; 2003 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Office of Educational Technology, 1993; 2004 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - SUNY Central - Finance and Business, 1993; 2000-2005 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - College of Arts and Sciences (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Department of Slavic Languages and Literatures and Germanic Languages and Literatures Merger (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Diversity Committees, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Rockefeller Colleges of Publc Affairs and Policy - Public Service Professor, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - CETL - Faculty Board, 1994; 1995 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - General Education, 1994; 1995 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - SED Doctoral Program Review, 1994; 1995 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Project Renaissance - Proposal, 1994; 1995; Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Doctoral Program Review, 1994; 1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - General Education, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Campus International Survey (1 of 2), 1994-1998; Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Campus International Survey (2 of 2), 1994-1998; Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Doctoral Program Review Screening Committee, 1994; 1996; 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Smart Classrooms, 1994; 1996-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Small Business Development Center, 1994; 1998; 1999; Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - CETL - Grants, 1994; 1995; 1999; 2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - CETL - Budget, 1994; 1995; 1999; ca. 2001; Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Departmental Graduate Assistantship Policies, 1994-1995; 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Surveys, 1994; 1996; 1997; 2001; 2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Project Renaissance, 1994-1999; 2003; Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Student Related Research Meeting (1 of 2), 1995 January 11-1995 January 12 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Student Related Research Meeting (2 of 2), 1995 January 11-1995 January 12 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Guidelines for the Preparation of Recommendations for Promotions and Continuing Appointments, 1995 September (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Dutch Studies, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Surveys - Peterson's Annual Survey of Higher Education Personnel, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Deans Correspondence, 1995; 1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Distinguished Professorship Nominations, 1995; 1996 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Student Employees Union, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - CETL, 1995; 1996; Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - University Senate - General, 1995; 1996; Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Project Renaissance, 1995-1998; Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Department of Geography and Planning, 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - School of Criminal Justice, Dean - Dean Bayley, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - School of Education, Dean - James Flemming, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments, 1995-1999; Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Project Renaissance - Budget, 1995-1999; Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Office of the Vice President for Research, 1995-2001 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Project Renaissance - Personnel, 1995; 1998; 1999; 2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Department of English, 1995; 1996; 1998-2002; Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Assistant Guideline, 1995-1996; 1999; 2000; 2002-2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Hitchcock Inauguration Participants, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Presidents' Report, suggested entries, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Master Plan, 1996; Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Tuition Opportunity Program, 1996; 1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - President's Report Submission, 1996; 1997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Innovation fund for Teaching, 1996; 1997; Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Master Plan - Research Subcommittee, 1996; 1997; Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Cyprus Program, 1996; 1997; 1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Surveys - LinguaFranca Hiring and Tenuring Survey, 1996; 1998 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Project Renaissance - Evaluation, 1996; 1997; 1998; Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Small Business Development Center - Director Search, 1996; 1998; 1999 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Institutional Research - Tuition Scholarship and waivers, 1996; 1998; 2000; 2001; Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Educational Opportunities Program (1 of 2), 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Educational Opportunities Program (2 of 2), 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Presidential Review, 1996; 1998; 2000-2002; Undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Master Plan - Supporting Material, ca. 1996 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Master Plan - Supporting Material, ca. 1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Extended Learning, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Innovation fund for Teaching - Proposals, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - NYSERNet - National Science Foundation Proposal, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Search file - Assistance Vice President for Alumni Affairs, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Surveys - NASULGC Economic Impact Survey, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Surveys - NASULGC Urban Public Service Activities Survey, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Master Plan, 1997; Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - CETL, 1997; 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - CETL - Peter Seldin Event, 1991; 1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Cyprus - International Education Fair, 1997; 1998 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Doctoral Review Panel, 1997; 1998 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Academic Council, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - NYSERNet ( 1 of 2), 1997; 1998 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - NYSERNet (2 of 2), 1997; 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Capital Region Software Alliance, 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Deans Correspondence (1 of 2), 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Deans Correspondence (2 of 2), 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid, Stipend Reports, 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Management Science and Information Systems, 1997; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Smart Classrooms, 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Office of the Vice President for Research, 1997; 1998; 1999 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Institutional Research - Outcomes Assessment, 1997-2000; Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Mission Review, 1997-2000; Undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Search File - Dean of the School of Public Health, 1997; 1999; 2000; 2001; Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - University Senate - General, 1997-2002; Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Commissioner's Doctoral Council (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Commissioner's Doctoral Council (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Dr. Nuala McGann Drescher Affirmative Action Leave Program, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - GRE, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - NYSERNet National Science Foundation Proposal, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Y2K Issues, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 2)